你们知道这是最后一次  我们以六个单身朋友的身分
Do you realize this is probably the last time we'll be here in the coffee house...
共聚一堂吗
...as six single people?
咖啡厅怎么了
What's happening to the coffee house?
噢  知道了
Oh! Okay.
从现在开始  是你们四个好朋友  我跟我太太了
Yep! From now on, it's gonna be the four of you guys and me and the missus.
我的小女人  好老婆  陈旧的婚姻枷锁
The little woman. The wife. The old ball and chain.
陈旧的  你是年轻性感的婚姻枷锁
Old? The young, hot ball and chain.
这还差不多  我们得走了
Much better. Op! We gotta go.
去哪里  我们去拿婚纱  然后跟妈妈一起吃午饭
Oh, where are you guys going? We're gonna pick up the wedding dress then we're gonna have lunch with mom.
乔伊  你也要去吃午饭
Ah. Joey you're-you're having lunch with my mom?
对啊  我只是听到 "午饭"
No, I-I just heard "lunch."
对  我也可以去啊  当然啦
But yeah, I can go. Sure.
其实  我很高兴他们都走了  因为
Y'know what? Actually, I'm kinda glad they're leaving. 'cause uh,
有一件事我得跟你谈一谈
I need to talk to you about something.
什么事  也许会有点尴尬
What's up? Well this uh, This may be a little awkward.
如果你需要钱  现在不是时候  明晚我得请128个人吃晚饭
Listen, if you want to borrow money, its kind of a bad time. I'm buying dinner for 128 people tomorrow.
不  不是那样的
No, it's not that.
我不是以你朋友的身分  跟你说话
now what I'm going to say to you, I’m not saying as your friend. Okay?
我要以摩妮卡大哥的身份跟你谈
... I'm-I'm saying as it as Monica's older brother.
但你还是我朋友吧  接下来的几分钟不是
But you're still my friend? Not for a few minutes.
那么现在  你还是我的伴郎吗  不是
During this time... are you, are you still my best man? Nope.
我还是可以叫你罗斯吗  当然
Do I still call you Ross? Okay.
你们快要结婚了  我真的很高兴
You guys are getting married tomorrow and-and I couldn't be more thrilled for both of you,
但身为她的大哥  我必须告诉你
But as Monica's older brother, I have to tell you this:
如果你胆敢伤害我妹妹
If you ever hurt my little sister...
如果你胆敢让她不快乐
...if you ever cause her any unhappiness of any kind...
我会把你摁倒在地
...I will hunt you down...
然后痛扁你
...and kick your ass.
你怎么啦   我是认真的
What? I'm-I'm-I'm serious!
兄弟  别闹了  我不是在开玩笑  我听到你的话了
Come—Hey! Dude! Stop it! Okay? I'm not kidding here! I hear what you're saying okay? and...
谢谢你的警告
...thanks for the warning.
别客气
No problem.
我们又是朋友了
So are we friends again?
对  好
Yeah. Okay.
你不会相信刚刚摩妮卡的哥哥都跟我说了些什么啊
Okay. You won't believe what Monica's older brother just said to me!
老友记  第七季  第23集  摩妮卡和钱德的婚礼(上集)
Friends  S07E23 The One With Chandler and Monica’s Wedding
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
你在做什么  摩妮卡
What you doing, Mon?
我在列出婚礼上可能会出差错的地方
I'm making a list of all the things that are most likely to go wrong at the wedding.
那样我可以做好准备
Now, that way I can be prepared.
会是些什么事出差错   目前为止  有伴娘的礼服忘了拿
Mm-hm. What are they? Well, so far I have uh, my bride's maids dresses won't get picked up,...
我婚纱的蒙面头纱不见  还有就是我忘了拿蓝色的东西
...my veil gets lost, or I don't have my something blue."
那些都是我负责的事啊
Hey! Those are all the things I'm responsible for.
我也必须以防万一
I had to go with the odds Rach.
喂  各位
Hey! You guys!
你们还记得之前我去试镜  没有拿到那个角色的事吗
Remember that audition I had a while ago, and I didn't get that part?
那个广告  不是
The commercial? No.
那出舞台剧  不是
That play? No.
另一出舞台剧  不是
That other play? Nooo!
那部电影  对
The movie? Yes!
那部关于飞行员和他的狗会开飞机的电影  不是
Yes that's the one about the pilot and his dog was plane? No.
不过  那件事也很伤我的心
But man, that one hurt.
这部电影在描述一次大战的士兵
This is the one about the soldiers who fight in World War I!
喔  不错呀  以前我们叫它 "大战"
Oh, yeah! Back then y'know, we called it "The Great War."
它真的是大战
It really was.
他们录取的那个角色不演了  希望我回去参演  我今天会有拍摄
Well anyway, the guy they wanted backed out and now they want me! I start shooting today!
恭喜  太好了
Congratulations! Oh that’s great!
等等  等等  可是今天你不能去  有晚宴彩排  我一定会赶过去的
Wait! Wait! Wait! You can't start today! Today's the rehearsal dinner. Oh no, I'll be done by then.
喔  那你快去吧  电影明星
Oh. Well then way to go, you big movie star!
对啊  待会见了各位  我要去跟纳粹作战了
I know! All right, I'll see you guys over there! I'm off to fight the Nazis.
等一下  乔伊  纳粹是我们在二次大战的敌人  不是一次大战
Oh, wait Joey. We fought the Nazis in WWII, not WWI.
好
Whoa. Okay.
谁是我们在一次大战的敌人
Yeah well, who-who was in WWI?
你说吧
Go ahead.
你要迟到了快去  好  晚点再见
You're gonna be late! Go! Go! Yeah, I'll see you.
谁是我们在一次大战的敌人
Who did We fight in WWI?
墨西哥  对  非常棒
Mexico? Yes. Very good.
（五十九号码头片厂）
嘿  乔伊  我们准备好了  我也是
Hey, Joey. We're ready. Yeah, me too.
理查  我们准备好了
Richard, we're ready for you.
乔伊崔比亚尼  这位是理查克洛斯比  他要饰演文森
Joey Tribbiani, This is Richard Crosby he's playing Vincent.
我要跟你演对手戏  很高兴能认识你乔伊
I'm doing my scenes with you? Nice to meet you Joey.
我不敢相信  这太不可思议了  你刚刚拿下奥斯卡金像奖
Wow! I can't believe this. This is incredible. I mean you just won an Oscar.
不  我没有
No, I didn't.
我知道你有
I think you did.
我想我落选了  三次
I think I lost, three times.
饼干  你要  不
Uh, cookie? Would you...? No.
再过一小时我们就要正式开拍了
Okay. We're about an hour away from getting the scene lit.
不介意的话  你们能对一下戏吗  好的  没问题
So, uh, if you guys don't mind, can we run it a couple of times? Yeah, sure.
好了  开始吧
Okay, all right. Let's do it.
开始
And action!
我们得找到其他士兵  算了吧  他们已经完了
We have to find the rest of the platoon! Forget the platoon. The platoon is gone!
什么  他们都死了  面对现实吧  东尼
What? The platoon's dead! Face facts, Tony!
我们该怎么办  我们没有援兵或食物
So what are we gonna do?!  We have no reinforcements! No-no food!
地下室有食物  有马铃薯跟一些意大利面
No, we still have food in the basement. I saw potatoes and some dry pasta.
等一下  乔伊  你一直在摸脸
Hang on a minute!  Joey, you keep touching your face.
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
不  没有
No. Nope,
我
I, uh...
我以为这么做会很酷
I thought it might be kind of a cool character thing.
他是个喜欢摸脸的人
Y'know? He's uh, he's a face toucher.
我可不那么认为
I don't think so.
我们从理查  最后一句台词开始  开始
Let's take it back to Richard's last lines. Action!
虽然我们没有武器  但我们还有食物  地下室有
We may not have any weapons, but we still have food.
马铃薯  意大利面
In the basement I saw potatoes, and some dry pasta...
跟几罐鲔鱼
...and a few tins of tuna!
甜心  我们得走了  好
Honey, we gotta go! Okay.
这个问题真的很难启齿
Okay. Here's a question you never want to ask:
我爸刚打来电话   问能不能借用你的珍珠项链
My dad just called and wants to know if he can borrow one of your pearl necklaces?
他有提到  戴哪种款式的吗
Did he say what kind of neckline he's wearing?
没有
No.
我只见过他一次  但我猜是低胸V字型的
Well. I've only met him once but I'm guessing, plunging?
他是那种 "不吓死人不罢休" 的爸爸
Yeah. He is more of a "if you've got it, flaunt it" kind of father.
我没有那种项链  我去问问瑞秋有没有
I don't have anything but let me go see if Rachel does.
对  让更多的人知道这件事
Yes, include more people in this.
你知道明天这个时候  我们就要结婚了吗
Okay. Do you realize that at this time tomorrow  we'll be getting married?
等等  我明晚好像有约了
Wait a minute! I have a date tomorrow night.
我不敢相信我们真的办到了  别一副很惊异的样子
I just, I can't believe we made it. Well you don't have to sound so surprised.
对不起  不过
I'm sorry, but...
没事  什么
Nothing. What?
老实说  自从我们订婚后
Well, honestly? Ever since we got engaged...
我一直在期待发生点什么事  好让你退缩
...I have been waited for something to, to flip you out.
真的吗  我也是
Honestly? Me too.
真的吗  对
Really? Yeah.
我以为会发生什么蠢事  然后我会做
Y'know I keep thinking that something stupid is gonna come up and I'll...
钱德会做的事
...go all Chandler.
但什么事都没发生  我很高兴
But nothing has. Ohh, I'm so glad.
谢谢你在这段时间  一直都非常镇定
Thank you so much for staying so calm during this.
这让我非常地冷静
I mean it's really, It's made me stay calm.
我可能会更差的  好
I could've been worse. Okay.
我马上回来
I'll be right there.
如果你在星期六前打电话来
Hi, if you're calling before Saturday...
这里是摩妮卡跟钱德家
...you've reached Monica and Chandler.
但如果你在星期六后打电话来  这里就是宾氏夫妇家
But if you're calling after Saturday, you've reached Mr. and Mrs. Bing.
请给宾氏夫妇留言
Please leave a message for the Bings!
嘿  玛琳  嗨
Hey Maureen! Hi.
天啊  她是我表妹玛琳  我们是宾氏夫妇
Gosh. Hey uh, Chandler? This is my cousin, Maureen. We're the Bings.
嗨  你们都很好看
Hi! Oh you guys look so beautiful.
宾先生跟宾太太
Mr. and Mrs. Bing!
哇  摩妮卡
Wow, Monica.
告诉你们  我以 "大哥的身分"跟钱德谈过
Hey, just so you know, I had my older-brother talk with Chandler.
你说了什么  嗯
What is that? Well, I...
我告诉他如果他胆敢伤害你
I told him that if he ever hurt you...
我会把他摁倒在地   然后痛扁他
...I would hunt him down and kick his ass.
怎么  怎么  大家是怎么了  我是认真的
What?! What?! What is the matter with everybody? I'm serious.
我会痛扁他
I would kick his ass!
罗斯  拜托  我的妆笑要掉了
Ross, please, my makeup!
嗨
Hi.
钱德  妈
Chandler. Mom.
谢谢你记得穿  衣服来
Thanks for wearing...something.
我真的很兴奋  我以为是我们害得你不敢结婚
Oh honey! This is so exciting! I thought we screwed you up so bad this day would never come.
你想想  很快地  你就会有一大堆姓宾氏的小孩
Oh and just think, soon there will be lots of little Bings.
我不敢相信我要回去  让人家继续喷口水
I can't believe I have to go back to work after this and get spit on again.
你很幸运   至少喷你口水的人都很有名
You're lucky. At least the people who spit on you are famous.
谁对你喷口水  我不想谈工作的事
Who spits on you? I don't wanna talk about work.
宾太太  他们是我爸妈  茱蒂跟杰克盖勒
Mrs. Bing? Here, These are my parents umm, Judy and Jack Geller.
很高兴能见到你  你是他妈妈还是他爸爸
It's lovely to meet you. So are you his mother or his father?
杰克
Jack!
干嘛   之前他父母我都没见过啊
What? I've never seen one before.
爸  罗斯在那边  去跟他谈一谈吧
Dad, there's Ross. why don't you go talk to him.
我不可能装作我一点都不在意这事啊
I didn't even have a chance to act as though I'm okay with it.
嘿  大家好
Hello, all.
嗨  爸爸
Hi...Dad.
嗨  宾先生
Hi, Mr. Bing.
诺扛  查尔斯
Nora. Charles.
很高兴你们两个都来了  对
It's so great to see you both here. Yes.
虽然有些人是衣不蔽体穿的少了点
Although I think we may be seeing a little too much of some people.
你不觉得自己稍微老了点   不适合穿成这样嘛
Aren't you a little old to be wearing a dress like that?
你不觉得自己是不是多了些东西   也不该穿成这样呢
Don't you have a little too much penis to be wearing a dress like that?
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你当然可以痛扁他  儿子
Of course you can kick his ass, son.
你想痛扁任何人都没有问题
You could kick anyone's ass you want to.
谢谢你们
Thanks, you guys.
瑞秋  干嘛
Rach, Rash? Yeah?
帮个忙  去跟钱德的老爸聊聊天  别让他跟钱德的老妈杠上了
Umm hey, could you do me a favor. and would talk to Chandler's dad and try to keep him away from Chandler's morn.
好  但我不知道他长什么样子  他穿着黑色洋装
Yeah, but I don't know what he looks like. He is the man in a black dress.
嗨  我是瑞秋  摩妮卡跟钱德的朋友
Hi. I'm Rachel, a friend of Monica and Chandler's.
我是亚曼达  喔  我懂了
I'm Amanda. Oh, I get it.
一个男人(音同亚曼达Amanda)  啊
"A man, duh!"
请大家听我说
Can I have everyone's attention please?
我是罗斯盖勒  罗斯盖勒博士
I'm uh; I'm Ross Geller. Dr. Ross Geller.
爸  拜托  我刚刚说过
Dad. Dad, please. As I was saying...
我是罗斯盖勒博士
...I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
我是伴郎
Uh, and I'm the best man.
这段婚姻对我来说有双重特殊意义
And this marriage is doubly special for me...
不仅仅因为新郎是我最好的朋友
...um, because not only is the groom my best friend...
更因为新娘是我的妹妹
...but, uh, the bride is my little sister.
她是所有男人  梦寐以求的好妹妹
She's the greatest sister a guy could ask for.
各位请跟我一起举起杯
So if you'd all please join me in raising a glass...
敬这对新人
...to the couple we're here to celebrate.
敬宾氏夫妇   敬宾氏夫妇
To the Bings. To the Bings!
好了  我要去熨婚纱了
All right, I'm gonna go steam my wedding dress okay?
谁负责确定它不会有问题
Who wants the responsibility of making sure nothing happens to it?
我会负责  谁要负责  有人愿意吗
I'll do it. Who wants it? Anybody?
我说了我会负责  没有人愿意吗
I said I'll do it. Nobody wants to do it?
好吧  那我就自己来  摩尼卡  我不会搞砸的
All right, I'll do it myself. Monica! I'm not gonna screw it up.
你说得对  对不起  今晚你帮了大忙
Y'know what? You're right. I'm sorry. Actually you were a big help tonight.
谢谢你帮忙  将我奶奶安全地送回饭店
Yeah, and thanks for putting my grandmother in the cab and making sure she got to the hotel safely.
当然  那就是我的工作  好吧  对不起
Well of course! That's what I'm here for. Okay. Sorry.
什么奶奶
What grandmother?
你跑到哪里去了  我送我爸妈回饭店
Hey! Where have you been? Oh, taking my parents back to the hotel.
你要回去工作了  对
What? Are you going back to work? Yeah.
很酷的太阳眼镜  谢谢夸奖  我想如果我能戴上它拍戏
Nice shades. Thanks. Yeah, I figure if I wear these in my scenes...
我的眼睛就不会喷到口水了
...at least I won't get spit in the eyes, y'know?
如果我没有记错  雷朋眼镜是一次大战的正式赞助商
And, if I remember correctly, Ray-Ban was the official sponsor of WWI.
那太棒了
Great!
晚点见  好吧
I'll see you later. All right.
钱德在哪里  我想他在瑞秋房间里  再见
Hey, where's Chandler? I think he's in Rachel's room. See you.
钱德
Chandler?
嘿  嗨
Hey. Hi.
摩妮卡在吗  她在熨婚纱  怎么了
Is Monica here? She's steaming her dress. Why? What's up?
我想钱德走了  什么
I think Chandler's gone. What?
他留下了这个  "告诉摩妮卡我很抱歉"
He left that. "Tell Monica I'm sorry."
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What's up?
"告诉摩妮卡我很抱歉"
"Tell Monica I'm sorry."
你自己去告诉她
Tell her yourself.
喔  我的天啊  钱德走了
Oh, my God. Chandler just left, though?
或许事情不是我们想的那样  或许他是说
Yeah but, maybe it's not what we think. Maybe it's:
"告诉摩妮卡我很抱歉   我把最后的牛奶都喝光了"
"Tell Monica I'm sorry I drank the last of the milk."
或许他写这张字条想告诉她  他改了名字
Or maybe he was writing to tell her that he's changed his name: y'know?
告诉摩妮卡  我叫 "抱歉"
Tell Monica, I'm Sorry.
这表示他很惊慌失措逃跑了  不要那么悲观
I think it means he freaked out and left! Don't be so negative!
天啊  有没有可能 "抱歉"   现在就坐在里面
Good God, isn't it possible that "Sorry" is sitting in there right now?
菲比  我想罗斯说得对  我们该怎么办
Okay. Phoebe, I think Ross is right. What are we gonna do?
我得去找他  把他带回来
Look—Okay, I'm just gonna-- I'm gonna have to go find him and bring him back. Okay?
你们别让摩妮卡发现  好吗
You make sure Monica does not find out, okay?
好  但是你如果没办法找到他  把他带回来
Okay? But, if you don't find him and bring him back...
我会把你摁倒在地   然后痛扁你
...I am gonna hunt you down and kick your ass!
我会  我会找到他的
I will, I will find him.
乔伊  你能跟我对一下台词吗
Hey Joey, Can you go through these lines with me?
喔  天啊  他们才帮我补好妆
Oh, man, they just re-did my makeup.
只要对最后两页  好吧
Just the last two pages. All right.
我发现照片了
I found the picture!
照片  什么照片
Picture? What picture?
我在你的背包里  发现我太太的照片
The picture of my wife! I found it in your pack!
你能不能把剧本放下来
Could you uh, could you lower your script?
我不愿意
I don't want to.
我得看到你的脸的表情  好作出反应来演出
I need to see your face so I can play off your reaction.
好吧  听我说
Okay, look.
我知道你的演技很棒   演过很多莎翁名剧
I know you're great actor, okay? And you play all those Shakespeare guys and stuff...
但你老是喷得我满脸是口水
...but you're spitting all over me, man.
那当然  你知道你会喷口水
Well of course I am! You know you've been spitting on me?
真正的演员都会那么做
That's what real actors do.
清晰地发音是一个好演员的特质
Enunciation is the mark of a good actor.
要清晰地发音  就要喷口水
And when you enunciate, you spit!
哇  还有这样的
Wow. Didn't know that.
谢了  好吧  看我的
Thanks. Okay, check it out.
照片  什么照片
Picture? What picture?
阿甘  你看到钱德了吗  不  我没有看到他
Gunther have you uh, have you seen Chandler? No, No. I haven't seen him.
该死  他明天要结婚了  对吧
Damn. He's getting married tomorrow, right?
对  别担心  一切都会没事的
Yes. Yes. Don't worry. Everything's fine.
明天婚礼上见  我没有被邀请
we'll see you at the wedding. I wasn't invited.
那么后天见
Well then we'll-we'll see you the day after tomorrow.
妈  爸
Morn? Dad?
你们在这里做什么
What-what…what you guys doing here?!
你们老是聊到这个地方  我们想看看这里有什么特别的
Well you kids talk about this place so much, we thought we'd see what all the fuss is about.
我知道为什么女孩们喜欢来这里  为什么
I certainly see why the girls like coming here. Why?
为了吧台后面那个金发性感大帅哥
The sexy blonde behind the counter.
阿甘  你妈刚把他列入她的名单
Gunther? Your mother just added him to her list.
什么  你的名单  我们可以上床的对象
What?  Your list? Yeah, the list that—Of people we're allowed to sleep--
不  不  我知道那是什么样的名单
Yes! No-no! I know, I know what the list is.
快坐下吧  喝杯咖啡
Sit down, have a cup of joe.
爸  我没空  抱歉
Dad? I can't, I'm sorry.
如果你们看到钱德  告诉他我在找他
Look if you see Chandler, could you just let him know I'm looking for him.
如果你看到丽塔莫雷诺  告诉她我在找她
And if you see Rita Moreno, let her know I'm looking for her.
开始
Action!
我发现照片了
I found the picture!
什么照片
What picture?
我在你的背包里  发现我太太的照片
A picture of my wife, in your pack!
你偷翻我的私人物品
You went through my personal property?
你的背包里  为什么会有宝丽蒂的照片
Why do you have a picture of Paulette in your pack?
文森  因为我们
Because, Vincent, we were lovers...
交往过两年
...for two years!
卡  太棒了
Cut! Wonderful!
真的是太棒了
Great scene, huh?
你真的很棒  最后那一段你喷得我的脸都湿了
You were awesome. And, in that last speech, you soaked me.
这是明天你的通告表  我明天没工作呀
Here's your call sheet for tomorrow. I'm not working tomorrow.
现在有了  不  不  你得帮我这个忙
You are now. No! No! I can't! you gotta get me out of it.
我已经有约了  这件事非常重要
I have got plans. Important plans!
罗斯说还是没有钱德的消息  喔  天啊
Ross said there's still no word from Chandler. Oh, man.
但他们发现  奶奶在第五大道上游荡
Oh but he did say that they found the grandmother wandering down 5th.
好吧  至少找到一个人了
Okay, well there's one down.
我今天要结婚了
I'm getting married today!
我断了一根肋骨  但我不在乎  因为我今天要结婚了
I think I just cracked a rib, but I don't care because today's my wedding day!
我终于要结婚了
My day is finally here!
或许她不会注意到他不见了
Y'know she might not even notice he's gone.
我要开始准备了
I'm gonna start getting ready!
我们不能让她开始准备  这太可怕了
God! Don't—We can't let her start getting ready. This is too awful!
等她换上婚纱  而他又没有出现
Oh God, but wait she'll be in the gown, and then he won't show up.
这时候她就得脱掉婚纱
and then she'll have to take off the gown--
停  冷静点  你不能在这里抓狂
Stop it. Stop it Rachel! You can't do this here.
对不起  抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
那真的是太伤感了
It's just...It's just so sad.
振作一点  别让她看到你这个样子
Yeah, but you've got to pull yourself together! Monica can't see you like this.
她会发现不对劲的  我知道  我知道
Then she'll know something's wrong. I know. I know.
天啊  没有面纸了
Oh God. There's no tissue.
你能拿张卫生纸给我吗
Can you grab me some toilet paper?
喔  卫生纸也没有了  这里是摩妮卡的浴室吧
Oh, that's gone too. This is Monica's bathroom, right?
我找到一张了  好吧
No-no! I-I...I found one. Okay.
谢谢
Oh thank you.
喔  天啊
Oh, God.
能再给我一张吗
Can I have another one?
没问题
Sure.
你需要牙线吗
Do you need some floss?
我无法想像如果钱德不出现  会发生什么事
Oh God I just can't imagine what will happen if Chandler doesn't show up.
这里有一大堆卫生纸
Oh here's a whole bunch.
她会穿着婚纱在礼堂等他
Oh, I mean she'll be at the wedding waiting for him ...
大家会窃窃私语  "喔  那个可怜的女孩"
...and people will be whispering, "Oh that poor girl."
然后她还得回到这里  独自一个人生活
Y'know? Then she'll have to come back here and live all alone.
喔  我的天啊  干嘛
Oh, my God. What?
垃圾桶有一根验孕棒  是阳性反应
There was a pregnancy test in the garbage, and it's positive.
摩妮卡怀孕了
Monica's pregnant.
我猜她不会寂寞了
So I guess she won't be totally alone.
下集提要
Next time on Friends:
我们得告诉她  他失踪了  不  我们不能那么做
We've gotta tell her that he's gone. No, we can't.
她很快就会开始做准备
She's gonna start getting ready soon.
你不能拖延她吗
Can't you stall her a little?
我永远都没办法结婚了
I'm never gonna get married.
我们只拍一场戏  就你跟理查  他是职业高手
We've just got one short scene. It's just you and Richard, and he's a pro.
你喝醉了吗  没有
Are you drunk? No!
你喝醉了  好吧
Yes, you are! All right.
钱德还好吗  他好极了
How's Chandler? Great!
你在哪里  我还在片场里
Where are you? On the set.
这将会是有史以来  最糟糕的一场婚礼
This is turning into the worst wedding day ever.